A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976; 3; 636.07 Cubic Feet 1659 containers - 1591 letter document boxes, 66 legal document boxes, 1 legal tall box, and 1 half-letter box.
  - Population, 1962-1976; 20; 20.69 Cubic Feet 52 letter document boxes and 2 legal boxes
    - Planned Parenthood Federation (Box 1055, Folder 2)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation - Joseph M. Jones Book (Box 1055, Folder 3)
    - Population Crisis Committee (Box 1055, Folder 4, Box 1056, Folder 1)
    - Population Education, Inc. (Box 1056, Folder 2-3, Box 1057, Folder 1)
    - Population Education, Inc. - Project on Human Sexuality - Fund Raising (Box 1057, Folder 2)
    - Population Education, Inc. - PEI Film (Box 1057, Folder 3)
    - Population Education, Inc - Fund Raising (Box 1057, Folder 4, Box 1058, Folder 1)
    - Population Institute (Box 1058, Folder 2-3)
    - Population Reference Bureau (Box 1058, Folder 4, Box 1059, Folder 1-3)
    - Population Reference Bureau - Latin American Project (Box 1059, Folder 4-5)
    - Population Reference Bureau - Contributions (Box 1059, Folder 6)
    - Population Reference Bureau - Printed material (Box 1060, Folder 1)
    - Printed Material (Box 1060, Folder 2-3, Box 1061, Folder 1)
    - JDR 3rd - Clippings (Box 1061, Folder 2-3)
    - JDR 3rd - Speeches re: Population Problem (Box 1061, Folder 4)
    - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau (Box 1062, Folder 1)
    - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau - JDR 3rd pledge (Box 1062, Folder 2-3)
    - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau - Mrs. Jean Mauze (Box 1064, Folder 4)
    - Mrs. Martha Stuart (Box 1063, Folder 1)
    - United Nations Fund for Population Activities (UNFPA) (Box 1063, Folder 2-4, Box 1064, Folder 1-2)
    - United Nations Fund for Population Activities (UNFPA) - Reports/Printed material (Box 1064, Folder 3)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment (Box 1064, Folder 5)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment - Meetings/Minutes (Box 1065, Folder 1)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment - Preparation of Report (Box 1065, Folder 2)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment - News Clippings (Box 1065, Folder 3)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment - Panel (Box 1065, Folder 4)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment - Report (Box 1066, Folder 1)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment - World Leaders Statement on Population I - U.S. Correspondence (Box 1066, Folder 2)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment - World Leaders Statements on Population - A-Z (Box 1066, Folder 3, Box 1067, Folder 1)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment - World Leaders Statement I (Box 1067, Folder 2-3)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment - World Leaders Statement I - Background papers (Box 1068, Folder 1)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment - World Leaders Statements on Population - Miscellaneous (Box 1068, Folder 2)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment - World Leaders Statement on Population I - Public Affairs (Box 1068, Folder 3)
    - United Nations/U.S.A. Panel on Population and the Quality of the Human Environment - World Leaders Statement II, 1974 (Box 1068, Folder 4)
    - United Nations World Population Conference Bucharest, 1974 (Box 1068, Folder 5-6)
    - United Nations World Population Conference Bucharest - Clippings, 1974 (Box 1069, Folder 1)
    - United Nations World Population Conference Bucharest - Population Tribune, 1974 (Box 1069, Folder 2)
    - United Nations World Population Conference Bucharest - Pathfinder Fund, 1974 (Box 1069, Folder 3)
    - United Nations World Population Year - Population Manifesto (Box 1069, Folder 4)
    - United Nations World Population Conference Bucharest - Post Bucharest, 1974 (Box 1070, Folder 1)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Formation (Box 1070, Folder 2)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future (Box 1070, Folder 3-5, Box 1071, Folder 1-3)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Clippings (Box 1071, Folder 4)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Finances (Box 1071, Folder 5)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Members (Box 1071, Folder 6, Box 1072, Folder 1)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Memoranda (Box 1072, Folder 2)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1072, Folder 3)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Printed Material (Box 1072, Folder 4)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - JDR 3rd - Appointments (Box 1072, Folder 5)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Report (Box 1073, Folder 1)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Report requests (Box 1073, Folder 2)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - JDR 3rd - Meeting, 1971 February 28 (Box 1073, Folder 3)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Staff (Box 1073, Folder 4)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - JDR 3rd - Notes (Box 1073, Folder 5)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - JDR 3rd - Arkansas hearings, 1971 June 7 (Box 1074, Folder 1)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - JDR 3rd - Washington hearings, 1971 April 15 (Box 1074, Folder 2)
    - USG - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future - Statements made before commission and reading material for the commission (Box 1074, Folder 3)
    - USG - Department of HEW Food and Drug Administration (Box 1074, Folder 4)
    - Citizens Committee on Population and the American Future (Box 1075, Folder 1-2)
    - Citizens Committee on Population and the American Future - A-Z (Box 1075, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Committee on Population and the American Future - Budget/Finances (Box 1075, Folder 4)
    - Citizens Committee on Population and the American Future - Printed Material (Box 1076, Folder 1)
    - Citizens Committee on Population and the American Future - Miscellaneous Contributions (Box 1076, Folder 2)
    - Citizens Committee on Population and the American Future - Fund Raising (Box 1076, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Committee on Population and the American Future - Land Use Conference (Box 1076, Folder 4)
    - Citizens Committee on Population and the American Future - Luncheon - Secular Organizations (Box 1076, Folder 5)
    - Citizens Committee on Population and the American Future - Luncheon - Religious Organizations (Box 1076, Folder 6)
    - Citizens Committee on Population and the American Future - Reports (Box 1077, Folder 1-2)
    - Citizens Committee on Population and the American Future - TV Program (Box 1077, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Committee on Population and the American Future - University of California School of Medicine - Health Policy Program (Box 1077, Folder 4)
    - USG - President's Committee on Population and Family Planning (Box 1078, Folder 1)
    - USG - President's Committee on Population and Family Planning - Printed material (Box 1078, Folder 2-3, Box 1079, Folder 2)
    - USG - President's Committee on Population and Family Planning - Reports/Papers (Box 1078, Folder 4)
    - USG - President's Committee on Population and Family Planning - Preparatory work (Box 1079, Folder 1)
    - University of Notre Dame Conference, 1963 (Box 1079, Folder 3)
    - Vatican (Box 1079, Folder 4)
    - Washington (Box 1079, Folder 5)
    - Zero Population Growth Inc. (Box 1080, Folder 1)
  - Q-R, 1962-1976; 21; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - R - Miscellaneous (Box 1080, Folder 3, Box 1081, Folder 1)
  - Race Relations, 1962-1976; 22; 7.11 Cubic Feet 15 letter document boxes and 3 legal document boxes
    - Race Relations - A-B (Box 1081, Folder 2-3)
    - Race Relations - C-I (Box 1082, Folder 1-2)
    - Race Relations - K-P (Box 1083, Folder 1-4)
    - Race Relations - R-Z (Box 1084, Folder 1-4)
    - Alabama Council on Human Relations (Box 1084, Folder 5)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corp. (Box 1085, Folder 1)
    - Blackstone Rangers (Box 1085, Folder 2)
    - Block Community Inc. (Box 1085, Folder 3)
    - Congress on Racial Equality (Box 1085, Folder 4)
    - Congress on Racial Equality - Printed Material (Box 1085, Folder 5)
    - Cornerstone Project (The) (Box 1086, Folder 1)
    - Institute for Southern Studies (Box 1086, Folder 2)
    - Interracial Council for Business Opportunities (Box 1086, Folder 3)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) (Box 1086, Folder 4, Box 1087, Folder 1)
    - NAACP - Legal Defense Fund - General (Box 1087, Folder 2-3, Box 1089, Folder 1)
    - NAACP - Legal Defense Fund - Rockefeller family Contributions (Box 1088, Folder 1)
    - NAACP - Legal Defense Fund - Contributions (Box 1088, Folder 2)
    - NAACP - Contributions - Special Contribution Fund (Box 1088, Folder 3, Box 1089, Folder 2-4)
    - National Association for Negro Musicians (Box 1089, Folder 5)
    - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing (Box 1090, Folder 1-4)
    - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing - Printed Material (Box 1090, Folder 5, Box 1091, Folder 1)
    - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing - 20th Anniversary Dinner (Box 1091, Folder 2)
    - National Committee on Tithing in Investment (Box 1091, Folder 3)
    - National Conference of Black Lawyers (Box 1091, Folder 4)
    - National Council of Negro Women (Box 1091, Folder 5)
    - National Urban League (Box 1092, Folder 1-4)
    - National Urban League - Development Foundation (Box 1093, Folder 1-2)
    - National Urban League - Housing Foundation (Box 1093, Folder 3, Box 1094, Folder 1)
    - New York Urban Coalition, Inc. (Box 1094, Folder 2-3)
    - New York Urban League (Box 1094, Folder 4-5)
    - Winrock Rockefeller Commerce & Industry Award (Box 1094, Folder 6)
    - Scholarship, Education and Defense Fund for Racial Equality, Inc. (Box 1095, Folder 1-2)
    - Scholarship, Education and Defense Fund for Racial Equality, Inc. - Contributions (Box 1095, Folder 3)
    - South African Institute of Race Relations (Box 1095, Folder 4)
    - Southern Christian Leadership Conference (Box 1095, Folder 5)
    - Southern Educational Conference, Inc. (The Southern Courier) (Box 1096, Folder 1)
    - Southern Regional Council, Inc. (Box 1096, Folder 2)
    - Southern Rural Research Project (Box 1096, Folder 3)
    - Student Christian Movement in New England (The) (Southern Courier) (Box 1096, Folder 4)
    - Urban Coalition (Box 1096, Folder 5)
    - Urban League of Westchester County, Inc. (Box 1096, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd (Box 1096, Folder 7)
    - Young, Kenneth J., Jr. Notes/Clippings (Box 1097, Folder 1)
    - Washington Research Project Action Council (Box 1097, Folder 2-4, Box 1098, Folder 1-3)
  - Real Estate, 1962-1976; 23; 52.85 Cubic Feet 128 letter document boxes and 9 legal document boxes
    - Real Estate - A-Z, 1
      - Real Estate - A-Z (Box 1099, Folder 1-3, Box 1100, Folder 1-4, Box 1101)
      - Cresap, McCormick and Paget Study (Box 1101, Folder 4)
      - Estate Good Hope - Finances (Box 1110, Folder 4)
      - Estate Good Hope - Meetings/Minutes (Box 1110, Folder 5)
      - Estate Good Hope - Public Affairs (Box 1110, Folder 6)
      - Estate Good Hope (Box 1110, Folder 7)
      - Hawks, Graham Dr. (Box 1118, Folder 3)
      - Interstate North (Box 1163, Folder 4-5, Box 1164, Folder 1-4)
      - Kahuku Venture - Printed Material (Box 1164, Folder 5)
      - Kahuku Venture (Box 1165, Folder 1)
      - Morningside Heights Inc. (Box 1171, Folder 1-3, Box 1172, Folder 1-2)
      - Morningside Heights Inc. - Housing Corporation (Box 1172, Folder 3)
      - Morningside Heights Inc. - Planner Position (Box 1172, Folder 4)
      - Morningside Heights Inc. - Contributions (Box 1172, Folder 5)
      - Morningside Heights Inc. - Printed Material (Box 1173, Folder 1-3)
      - Mountain Park (Box 1174, Folder 1)
      - Mutual Real Estate Investment Trust (Box 1174, Folder 2)
      - Panola Associates (Fairington) (Box 1186, Folder 2-3)
      - Panola Associates (Fairington) - Finances and Partnership Agreements (Box 1187, Folder 1-5, Box 1188, Folder 1-4)
      - West 55th St. Rockefeller Garage (Box 1224, Folder 1)
    - Embarcadero Center, 2
      - Embarcadero Center (Box 1101, Folder 5, Box 1103, Folder 2)
      - Embarcadero Center - A-Z (Box 1102, Folder 1-4, Box 1103, Folder 1)
      - Applicants (Box 1103, Folder 3)
      - Clippings (Box 1103, Folder 4, Box 1104, Folder 1)
      - Articles (Box 1104, Folder 2)
      - Design/Construction - Controversy (Box 1104, Folder 3)
      - Documents (Box 1104, Folder 4)
      - Meeting (Box 1104, Folder 5)
      - Embarcadero Center Associates (Box 1104, Folder 6, Box 1105, Folder 1-2)
      - Finances (Box 1105, Folder 3, Box 1106, Folder 1-4)
      - Hotels (Box 1106, Folder 5-6)
      - Hyatt Regency Hotel (Box 1107, Folder 1-3)
      - International Affair Center (Box 1107, Folder 4)
      - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1108, Folder 1-2)
      - Levi Straus Building (Block 231) (Box 1108, Folder 3, Box 1109, Folder 1-2)
      - Levi Straus Building (Block 232) (Box 1109, Folder 3)
      - PIC Realty Co. (Box 1110, Folder 1)
      - Public Relations (Box 1110, Folder 2)
      - Reports (Box 1110, Folder 3)
      - David Rockefeller - Partnership Restructuring, 1976-1977 (Box 1654, Folder 1)
    - Estate Fountain River Company, 3
      - Estate Fountain River Company (Box 1111, Folder 1, Box 1112, Folder 1-2, Box 1116, Folder 4)
      - Estate Fountain River Company - A-Z (Box 1111, Folder 2-3)
      - Appraisal and Sales Proposals (Box 1112, Folder 3)
      - Contributions (Box 1112, Folder 4)
      - Development Program (Box 1112, Folder 5)
      - Finances (Box 1113, Folder 1-3, Box 1114, Folder 1)
      - Finances/Expenditures (Box 1114, Folder 2)
      - Golf Course and Pro Shop-Planning Construction (Box 1114, Folder 3)
      - Hotel (Box 1114, Folder 4)
      - Hotel Feasibility Study Cresap/McCormick (Box 1115, Folder 1)
      - James D. Landauer Associates, Inc. (Box 1115, Folder 2-3, Box 1116, Folder 1-2)
      - Opening (Box 1116, Folder 3)
      - David Rockefeller Office Memos (Box 1117, Folder 1)
      - Park Proposal (Box 1117, Folder 2-4)
      - Sale of Property (Box 1118, Folder 1)
      - Sea Pines Plantation (Box 1118, Folder 2)
    - Hills Realty, 4
      - Hills Realty (Box 1119, Folder 1, 3)
      - Sale (Box 1119, Folder 2)
      - Siegesmund C.E. (Box 1119, Folder 4)
      - Edison Industrial Center (Box 1119, Folder 5, Box 1120, Folder 2-3)
      - Edison Properties (Box 1120, Folder 1)
      - Edison Industrial Center - Park/Bernet Joint Correspondence (Box 1120, Folder 4)
      - Carlyle Hotel (Box 1120, Folder 5, Box 1121, Folder 1)
      - Carlyle Hotel - Moorestown Mall Shopping Center (Box 1121, Folder 2-3, Box 1122, Folder 1-3, Box 1123, Folder 1-2)
      - Finances (Box 1123, Folder 3-4, Box 1124, Folder 1)
      - Legal (Box 1124, Folder 2)
      - Maps/Surveys (Box 1124, Folder 3)
      - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1125, Folder 1)
      - Parke Bernet Property (Box 1125, Folder 2-3)
      - Site Sale (Box 1125, Folder 4)
      - Greenrock Corporation (Box 1126, Folder 1-2)
        Restricted - Open in 2042
      - Greenrock Corporation - Budget (Box 1126, Folder 3)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Clippings (Box 1126, Folder 4)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Finances (Box 1127, Folder 1, Box 1128, Box 1129, Folder 1-2)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Financial Statements (Box 1127, Folder 2-3)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1129, Folder 3-4, Box 1130, Folder 1)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - A-Z (Box 1130, Folder 2-3, Box 1131, Folder 1-4)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Articles (Box 1131, Folder 5)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Bearss Study (Box 1132, Folder 1)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Bridal Path (Box 1132, Folder 2-3)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Budget (Box 1132, Folder 4-6, Box 1133, Folder 1-3)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Christmas gifts (Box 1133, Folder 4)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Clippings (Box 1133, Folder 5-6)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Contributions (Box 1133, Folder 7)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Contracts/Estimates (Box 1134, Folder 1)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - General Correspondence (Box 1134, Folder 2)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Employees (Box 1134, Folder 3-5, Box 1135, Folder 1-4)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Equipment (Box 1135, Folder 5)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Finances (Box 1135, Folder 6-8)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Fire Districts (Box 1136, Folder 1)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Hilltop Engine Co. 1 (Box 1136, Folder 2)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Housing (Box 1136, Folder 3)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Hunting & Fishing (Box 1136, Folder 4)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Inquiries (Box 1136, Folder 5)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Insurance (Box 1136, Folder 6)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Japanese brook (Box 1136, Folder 7)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - National Park Service (Box 1136, Folder 8)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit (Box 1136, Folder 9-10)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit gates (Box 1137, Folder 1)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Legal (Box 1137, Folder 2)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Liquidation (Box 1137, Folder 3-4)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Memos (Box 1137, Folder 5)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1137, Folder 6)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Plantings (Box 1137, Folder 7)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - National Historic Landmark (Box 1138, Folder 1)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Playhouse (Box 1138, Folder 2-4)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Review Committee (Box 1138, Folder 5, Box 1139, Folder 1)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Property (Box 1139, Folder 2-4, Box 1140, Folder 1-4, Box 1141, Folder 1-5, Box 1142, Folder 1-3)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Property (Box 1143, Folder 1-5, Box 1144, Folder 1-4, Box 1145, Folder 1-6, Box 1146, Box 1147, Folder 1-3, Box 1148)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor (Box 1149, Folder 1)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - A-Z (Box 1149, Folder 2-3)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Maine - General Correspondence (Box 1149, Folder 4)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Proposed Seal Harbor Foundation (Box 1149, Folder 5)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Acadia Corp. (Box 1149, Folder 6)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Asti-Kim Corporation (Box 1149, Folder 7-8, Box 1150, Folder 1-5, Box 1151, Box 1152, Folder 1-8, Box 1153, Folder 1-4, Box 1154)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Budget (Box 1155, Folder 1-3, Box 1156, Folder 1-2)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Equipment (Box 1156, Folder 3)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Expenditures (Box 1156, Folder 4)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Finances (Box 1156, Folder 5-6)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Maps (Box 1157, Folder 1)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Mount Desert Development Corp. (Box 1157, Folder 2)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Mount Desert Summer-Year Round Resident Planning Committee (Box 1157, Folder 3-5, Box 1158, Folder 1-2)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - General Correspondence (Box 1158, Folder 3)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - A-Z (Box 1159, Folder 1-5)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Acadia National Park (Box 1159, Folder 6, Box 1160, Folder 1)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Land Purchases (Box 1160, Folder 2-3)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Land Sales (Box 1160, Folder 4-11, Box 1161, Folder 1-15)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Rental Houses (Box 1161, Folder 16-17)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Seaside Inn (Box 1161, Folder 18)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Trust (Box 1161, Folder 19)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Planning (Box 1162, Folder 1)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Rockefeller, Abby A. Gardens (Eyrie Gardens) (Box 1162, Folder 2-5, Box 1163, Folder 1)
      - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Seal Harbor Water Company (Box 1163, Folder 2-3)
    - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation, 5
      - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation (Box 1165, Folder 2-3)
      - Construction - Contractors (Box 1165, Folder 4)
      - District of Columbia Redevelopment Land Agency (Box 1166, Folder 1)
      - Clippings (Box 1166, Folder 2-3)
      - Cost and Cash Flow Projections (Box 1166, Folder 4, Box 1167, Folder 1)
      - Change Orders (Box 1167, Folder 2-3)
      - Finances (Box 1167, Folder 4-5, Box 1168, Folder 1)
      - Printed Material (Box 1168, Folder 2)
      - Overlook and Ramp Construction (Box 1168, Folder 3, Box 1170, Folder 1)
      - Loews L'Enfant Plaza Hotel (Box 1168, Folder 4)
      - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1168, Folder 5, Box 1169, Folder 1)
      - Directors Meetings (Box 1169, Folder 2-3)
      - Opening (Box 1169, Folder 4)
      - Progress Reports (Box 1170, Folder 2)
      - Subscription Calls (Box 1170, Folder 3)
      - West Building (Box 1170, Folder 4-7)
    - Pacific Air Commerce Center, Inc., 6
      - Pacific Air Commerce Center, Inc. (Box 1174, Folder 3-4, Box 1175, Folder 1-2)
        Named changed to Westbay Community Associates
      - Articles (Box 1176, Folder 1)
      - Board of Directors (Box 1176, Folder 2)
      - Clippings (Box 1176, Folder 3-4)
      - Expenditures (Box 1176, Folder 5)
      - Ideal Basic Industries (merger) (Box 1177, Folder 1)
      - Legal (Box 1177, Folder 2)
      - Lindquist memos (Box 1177, Folder 3)
      - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1177, Folder 4)
      - Meyers, Andre (Box 1177, Folder 5)
      - Printed Material (Box 1177, Folder 6, Box 1178, Folder 1)
      - Public Affairs (Box 1178, Folder 2)
      - Stock Subscription (Box 1178, Folder 3)
    - Westbay Community Associates, 7
      - Westbay Community Associates - A-Z (Box 1178, Folder 4-6, Box 1179, Folder 1)
        Formerly Pacific Air Commerce Center
      - Westbay Community Associates (Box 1179, Folder 2)
        Formerly Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc.
      - Clippings (Box 1179, Folder 3, Box 1180, Folder 1)
      - Coyote Point (Box 1180, Folder 2)